gkseries.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy - www.gkseries.com

We respect the privacy of everyone who visits Gkseries.com. In some pages of our website you are asked to submit your personal data and that is why we would like to inform you regarding the way we would use your personal data. We recommend you to read this privacy policy so that you understand our approach towards the use of your personal data. By submitting your personal data to us, you will be treated as having given your permission – where necessary and appropriate – for disclosures referred to in this policy.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy:

By using our website through any device, you will be bounding to our Privacy Policy. If you feel unsatisfied with our privacy policy or terms and conditions please discontinue using our website.

### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This privacy policy is to inform you regarding the use of your personal information which is collected during your visit to Gkseries.com.

### Security of your personal data

We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Gkseries.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site and third party websites. Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Site, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.

### Changes to this policy

From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any substantial changes to this privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal data we will post these changes on this page and will do our best to notify you of any significant changes. Please check our privacy policy on a regular basis.

### How you can contact us

If you would like to contact Gkseries.com about our privacy policy, please mail us at **utpal@gkseries.com**
